Guide to the Robert Ensko Inc. Records 1787-1798, 1908-1978 (bulk 1934-1970) MS 200
New-York Historical Society
- Series V. Sales Tickets and Invoices, 1941-1970; 87 Linear feet
  - Subseries V.C. Client Invoices, 1946-1970; 26 Linear feet
    - Client invoices, 1961 (Offsite-box 177)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 69145-70384 (April 1961-June 1961), 70385-71264 (July 1961-Sept 1961), 71265-72532 (Oct 1961-Dec 1961).
    - Client invoices, 1962 (Offsite-box 178)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 72533-73523 (Jan 1962-March 1962), 73524-74759 (April 1962-June 1962), 74760-76053 (July 1962-Oct 1962).
    - Client invoices, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 179)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 76054-76932 (Nov 1962-Dec 1962), 76933-77785 (Jan 1963-March 1963), 77786-78851 (April 1963-June 1963).
    - Client invoices, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 180)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 78852-79619 (July 1963-Sept 1963), 79620-80624 (Oct 1963-Dec 1963), 80625-81372 (Jan 1964-March 1964).
    - Client invoices, 1964 (Offsite-box 181)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 81373-82265 (April 1964-June 1964), 82266-82869 (July 1964-Sept 1964), 82870-83813 (Oct 1964-Dec 1964).
    - Client invoices, 1965 (Offsite-box 182)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 83814-84631 (Jan 1965-May 1965), 84632-85259 (June 1965-Sept 1965), 85260-85842 (Oct 1965-Dec 1965).
    - Client invoices, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 183)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 85843-86714 (Jan 1966-June 1966), 86715-87576 (July 1966-Dec 1966), 87577-88388 (Jan 1967-June 1967).
    - Client invoices, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 184)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 88389-89212 (July 1967-Dec 1967), 89213-89913 (Jan 1968-June 1968), 89914-90537 (July 1968-Dec 1968).
    - Client invoices, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 185)
      The box holds three stacks of bills numbered 90538-91177 (Jan 1969-June 1969), 91178-91706 (July 1969-Dec 1969), 91707-92373 (Jan 1970-May 1970).